(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T02:13:27.531314",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ここはねぽらぼ学園！
This is Nepolabo Academy!
部活もクラスも違うけど、ねねたち同じ学生寮に住んでるんだー！
We're in different clubs and classes, but we all live in the same dorm!
ふざけて、笑って、時々喧嘩して…
Joking around, laughing, fighting sometimes...
でも、アスマルといるとなんか落ち着く！
but being with Asumaru somehow makes me feel at ease!
今日も談話室賑やか。
The common room is lively today.
誰かの声が聞こえるだけで、安心するんだよね。
Just hearing someone's voice makes me feel at ease.
この場所で私たちだけの学寮祭を作るなんて、楽しそう手ワクワクするな。
Creating a school festival just for us here sounds so much fun, I'm so excited.
さあ！
Now,
私たちの！
our...
輝く青春が！
shining youth...
始まる！
begins!
ねぽらぼ学園 5周年記念！！輝く学寮祭★
Nepolabo Academy 5th Anniversary!! Shining School Festival★
今日は学寮祭！
Today is the school festival!
生徒会が中心になって開催する、夏の一大イベント！
A huge summer event organized mainly by the student council!
会長からの頼みで、急遽ねぽらぼで出し物を考えることになったんだけど──
At the student council president's request, Nepolabo suddenly had to think up a booth, but──
何も考えられてなーーい！！！
We haven't thought of anything at allll!!!
やばいよ…気づいたら、もう当日だよ〜〜〜！
This is bad... Before we knew it, today's the dayyy!
だから言ったじゃんもっと早く集まって決めようって！
I told you guys we should've gotten together earlier and decided!
いやーなんとかなるって思ってたんだけどな〜（笑）
Man, I thought it'd somehow work out, haha~
うう…これはヤバい…
Ugh... This is bad...
変なことやったら、会長になて言われるか……
If we do something weird, what will the president say to us...
(──────)
(......)
よっし、断ろう！！
Alright, let's turn it down!!
やめな！当日に断れるわけないでしょ！
Stop that! There's no way we can turn it down on the day of!
大丈夫大丈夫、ラミちゃんならきっと許してくれて♪
It's fine, it's fine, Lamy-chan will surely forgive us♪
くれるって。
なんでラミィだけが前提なのよっ！
Why is only Lamy's premise getting accepted?
…いや、まだ終わってない！！
...No, it's not over yet!!
学祭はお昼から…
The school festival starts at noon, so...
ほんのちょっとだけ、まだ時間はあル！
Just a little bit more, there's still time!
よし、とりあえず案を出してみよっか。
Alright, let's at least brainstorm something.
学校の祭りといえば…焼きそば、じゃがバター、唐揚げ、クレープ、ポテト…
When it comes to school festivals... yakisoba, buttered potatoes, karaage, crepes, potatoes...
食べ物しかないじゃん！！
That's just food!!
…でも今からの仕込みはまあちょっと無理かもな。
...But starting preparations from now is probably impossible.
まあできるとしたら炎天下でカラカラな喉に染みわたる、ラミィ水！！これは売れるぞー！
Well, if we could do something... Lamy's water, soaking down our scorching-hot, parched throats! This is gonna sell!
やめろぉぉぉ！！！
Cut it out!
うっひょぉぉお！しぼり出して〜
Uuh, squeeze it out~
バカなこと言ってないで！もっと真面目に考えなさいて！
Stop saying stupid things and think about it more seriously!
そんなに言うならラミィちゃんは何がいいの？
If you say so, what does Lamy want?
ラミィ？
Me?
そうだなあ…やっぱり歌は歌いたいし…バンドとか、かな？
Let's see... Singing is always great, maybe a band or something?
ふつう。
How ordinary.
ひねりがなーい。
Lacks a twist—
フフッ（笑）
Hehe.
こいつら…！
These guys...!
でもまあ、歌はいいかもね〜
Well, singing is nice too, though.
ショート動画用にいろいろな曲練習してるし、その中から何かやってみる？
We've been practicing various songs for short videos, so maybe we could do one of those?
あっ、じゃあねね、あれやりたい！！元気いっぱいの、ねねたちにピッタリなやつ！！
Ah, Nene, I want to do that one!! That energetic song perfect for us Nenes!
あーー！あれね！
Ah, that one!
いいんじゃない！
Isn't that great?
じゃ、とりあえずやってみますか！
Well, let's try doing it for now!
キメマスター！！
Kime Master!
前人ゼロの未踏地だよなあ (そいやー！)
An uncharted frontier of our own (Soiya!)
生れ変わる一歩目は一歩目が大事さ 恐れないでやん、ど
The first step defines everything, don't be afraid!
何度も平気な顔で走り出して
Even if we stumble, we run out with a straight face!
行かなきゃ！上々の気分さ
Got to move forward! With the highest spirits!
やってみたいことには欲張りだね
Be greedy for what you want to try!
欲張りごめんね 直さないよっ
Being greedy? Sorry, I won't hold back!
何度も未来を書き換えたくなるのさ
Wanting to rewrite the future over and over!
行かなきゃ！最高の仲間と
Got to go! With the greatest companions,
星になろうよ 輝きたいよ 今はたださ
Let's become stars, let's shine brightly!
後悔しないようにねっ
So we don't regret it later!
さあおいで MONSTERS 暴れちゃお MONSTERS
So dance on, MONSTERS! Go wild, MONSTERS!
こんなにも無敵 PIKA STARS !
Such invincible PIKA STARS!
夢がキラキラ 無駄にキラキラ??
Dreams are sparkly, is it a waste to be sparkly??
前進だ DOKA-DOKA !!
Surging forward with a DOKA-DOKA!!
(はわっ 通りまるー!)
(Whoa, passing through!)
きまっちゃってる!?
Nailed it?!
全速モードでよいしょっしょ 制限は無視だよ
Full speed mode, yay, yay, rules are meant to be ignored!
なんでもかんでもやっぱっぱ 全力がいいよね
No matter what, going all out is best!
笑顔あり キメ顔アリ 最強 BIG BANG 狙っちゃえ未来 !
Smile and a nailed pose! Let's aim for the ultimate BIG BANG!
(チェストー !)
(Chest!)
手と手合わさるんだったら怖くないよね
Holding hands, there's nothing to be scared of!
夢の計測メーターは振り切れそうだよ
The dream's gauge meter is about to max out!
地球からやってきたボクらは 本日も Go ahead ! Go ahead !
We've come from Earth, today too, Go ahead! Go ahead!
怒られても…怒られても止まれないのです
Even if we get scolded, we can't stop!
騒々しくてもごめんなさーい !
Sorry for being so noisy!
先陣誰だい？ボクだい！
Who's the vanguard? It's us!
いわゆる前人ゼロの未踏地だよなあ (そいやー！)
An uncharted frontier of our own (Soiya!)
ゆずらないないない百歩目も 百歩ゆずるなんて負けよ負けよ
Even a hundred steps where we don't yield—
ゴールへのロードは砂利と岩だらけで
The road to the goal is full of gravel and rocks,
泣いても顔は “に・や・り”
Even if we cry, our faces are wreathed in smirks!
そんな時あきらめ悪く進め だってほらあきらめたくない夢が
Even so, we want to keep moving forward,
進化してみんなを果ての果ての空へ
Evolving, taking everyone to the furthest skies!
連れ去るボクら地球女子
Left behind, we are Earth girls!
憧れたんだ 星の光は消えないときめき
We longed for it, starlight that never fades!
心拍数上がりまくりっさあ踊れ MONSTERS
Heartbeat going crazy, so dance on, MONSTERS!
暴れちゃお MONSTERS 大胆で不敵 PIKA STARS !
Go wild, MONSTERS! Boldly, PIKA STARS!
随時きらめきが上昇中つまり好調中
Sparkles ever rising, meaning we're doing great!
(あ、サビきまーす)
(Ah, chorus time!)
多分勝利は、キマっちゃってる！
Victory is practically in the bag!
バンドじゃないからせせせせカッコつけなければ バンドじゃないからよよよよカッコがつくのだよ
It's not a band, so let's put on a cool show!
バカ騒ぎやんちゃ騒ぎやったもん勝ち狙っちゃえ未来！
Raising a ruckus, whoever makes a fuss wins, let's claim the future!
(チェストー！)
(Chest!)
銀河のどっかの頂点に旗を立てるまで ニューなレコードの更新は続くんだってば
Planting our flag at the galaxy's peak, breaking new records!
地球からやってきたボクらよやりまくれ Go ahead ! Go ahead !
We've come from Earth, so let's do it, Go ahead! Go ahead!
さあ次の星へ！
On to the next star!
一歩が百歩の始まりだから行こうよすぐに行こうよ
The first step is the start of a hundred, so let's go right away!
無理は道理よりも強引だなー 瞬間をキミと一緒にね monsters !!
Being unreasonable is stronger than logic, let's share this moment together, monsters!!
真っ暗な空かもしれないけれどボクらは輝きたい
It might be pitch dark, but we want to shine!
お目々を開いてお目々を離すなよー？
Keep your eyes open, don't look away!
もすたーえー もすたーえー もすたーえー
Monsters! Monsters! Monsters!
前人未踏の宇宙に全速の全力で GO だ yeah !!
With full speed and full power into the unprecedented universe, GO yeah!!
楽観だいそうだそうだい地球はブルーだブルーだっ
Optimism, that's right, Earth is blue, blue!
そうだ、そうだっ
That's right, that's right!
地球はブルーだ、ブルーだっ
Earth is blue, so blue!
全部を欲しがれ EARTH女子!
Want it all, Earth girls!
全開 そうかも、そうかもっ
Full throttle, could it be, could it be?
宇宙のスターに、スターになりたい?
Want to become a star of the universe?
なりたい! なりたい!
I want to! I want to!
なれそう? なれそうだよ!
Can we make it? Yes, we can!
キマっちゃったね!
We nailed it!
全速モードでいよっしょっしょ 制限は無視だよ
Full speed ahead, ignore the limits!
なんでもかんでもやっぱっやっぱ全力がいいよね
Going all out in everything is the best!
笑顔終わり 日替わり 最強BIG BANG!
Smiles change daily, the ultimate BIG BANG!
狙っちゃえ未来! チェストー!
Aim for the future! Let's go!
手を取り合ったらんだった 怖くないよね
Hand in hand dancing along, nothing to fear!
夢の計測メーターは 振り切れそうだよ
Our dream meter is about to go off the charts!
地球からやってきたボクらは 本日も Go ahead! Go ahead!
Coming from Earth, we're going ahead today too!
…怒られるまで
...Until we get scolded!
…怒られても止まれないのです
...Even if we get scolded, we can't stop!
最後の最後もごめんなさーい!
Sorry right till the very end!
先陣どだい? ボクらだい!
Leading the charge? That's us!
いわゆる前人未踏の未踏地だよなあ
Truly uncharted territory!
大いなる一歩さ ボクらと最高で
A giant leap, with us, to the absolute best!
前人未踏の未踏地へ Go!! そいやっ!
To uncharted territory, Go!! Here we go!
よ～し次はバンドだ！できる曲を片っ端からやっていこう～！！
Alright, next is a band! Let's play whatever songs we can!
でもわたしたち、楽器できなくない…？
But wait, can we even play instruments...?
いや、こういうのはね、雰囲気か大事！頑張っている姿を見せれば、それでOK！
Well, in these things, vibe is what matters! Show you're trying, and that's OK!
バカにしといて結局やるのね…
You brush it off, but you end up doing it anyway...
じゃあまず、誰が何やるか決めよ～！ねねはギターっ！！
First, let's decide who plays what! Nene's on guitar!!
じゃあししろんはドラムかな～
Guess Shishiron's on drums~
ポルカは…ベースで～！
And Polka's on... bass~!
…じゃあラミィは…シンセ、やろうかなっ
...Then Lamy will... do the synth.
そしたら演出も考えないとな～
Then we gotta think about the stage production too~
派手にドッカ～ンってしたい！！
I want it to go kaboom in a flashy way!!
ざっくりだな～
That's pretty vague~
サビにキャノンとか出す?
Shoot off canons during the chorus or something?
いいね！照明もレーザー出したりとかでピカピカにしていこう！
Sounds good! Let's make it flashy with lights and lasers!
よし、じゃあねねはポルカと動き回ってパフォーマンスしよう！
Alright, Nene, let's move around and perform with Polka!
やるやる、任せて～!!
You got it, leave it to me!!
だ、大丈夫か? 間に合わなくってアタフタするんじゃない?
A-Are you sure? Won't you panic if you can't make it in time?
ま、それも「わたしたちらしさ」ってことで～
Well, that's just part of "being us"~
さ、ノリでなんとかなるなる！
Come on, we'll get by on pure vibes!
…あ、そうだ。バンド名、どうするの?
...Ah, right. What's the band name gonna be?
えっ！かっこいいやつがいいな～!!
Eh! Something cool would be nice~!!
え、じゃあ…「青春ピチピチフルスロットル団!!」
Uh, then... "Youth Pichi-Pichi Full Throttle Crew!!"
…だ、ダサっ!?!?
...T-Tacky!?!?
あー、もうちょい期生要素も入れたいね。ラーメン、バリバリき、低気圧……
Ah, I want to include more generation elements. Ramen, shaved ice, low pressure......
「カブトムシ」って入れたらかっこいいよ!!
Putting "Rhinoceros Beetle" in makes it cool!!
「青春低気圧★ラーメンピチピチフルスロットルバリバリキダン」
"Youth Low Pressure★Ramen Pichi-Pichi Full Throttle Shaved Ice Crew"
混ぜるな！ぐちゃぐチャだよっ…
Don't mix them! It's a total mess...
ええ、じゃあラミィちゃんは何がいいの?
Eh, then what do you want, Lamy-chan?
え～やっぱり可愛いのがいいかなぁ～「ねぽらぼハーモニー」とか～♪
E~h, I guess something cute would be nice~ Like "Nepolabo Harmony"~♪
それでいいのかラミィ
Is that really fine, Lamy?
かっこよくないよ、ラミィ
That's not cool, Lamy.
俺、恥ずかしいよラミィ
I'm embarrassed, Lamy.
ほんとに……お前らっ!!
Seriously... you guys!!
よ～し！バンド名も決まったし、やってみますか～!!
Alright! The band name's decided, so let's try it out~!!
これで、学祭祭の注目はいただきだーーっ!!
Alright, with this, all attention at the school festival is ours!!
えっ!? あれで行くの!?
Eh!? We're going with that!?
いくぞーーっ!! よいしょーーいっ!! どんっ!!
Let's goーー!! Here we goーー!! Boom!!
走って走って 憧れを越えて
Running, running, surpassing our aspirations,
Ready!! Steady!! Derby!!
まだ見たことないスピードの向こう側へ
Toward the other side of a speed we've never seen before,
ワンラップは完璧さ！
One lap is perfection!
地球をほら 踏み込む鉄蹄
Look at the iron hooves stepping onto Earth,
ゴール前の奇跡
A miracle before the finish line!
仕掛ける場所は最終コーナー
The place to make our move is the final corner!
あとは行けるところまでいきおい出したい！
From there, we want to push our momentum as far as we can go!
何万回も手を叩くオーディエンス 割れんばかり響く大歓声
The audience clapping tens of thousands of times, deafening loud cheers resounding,
ファンファーレが鳴る 心音が高まる
The fanfare sounds, our heartbeats rise,
動き出す秒針 夢のゲートが開く 行くぞ！
The second hand moves, the gate of dreams opens, let's go!
走って走って 憧れを追い越して 次は誰の番だ！？
Running, running, overtaking our aspirations, whose turn is next!?
冷めきったスパーク
A cool, clear spark!
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Now, aiming to be a superstar,
生きてく
Living...
意味なんて
What's the meaning of it...
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
It follows right after breaking away,
勝ちたい！
I want to win!
そう、これは本能
Yes, this is instinct.
走りたい！
I want to run!
やまない衝動
An unceasing impulse.
叫びたい！
I want to shout!
勝利の雄叫びよ 轟け！
Roar, the shout of victory!
誰かとバチバチ競うことでしか
Only by sparking and competing with someone
到達得ない輝かしいゴールライン
can we reach that dazzling goal line.
ah どんな理屈でも言語化できない感情
Ah, emotions that no logic can put into words,
科学を超えて オカルトを超えて
surpassing science, surpassing the occult,
熱い勝負したい！したい！したい！
we want an intense match! Want! Want!
どちらが最強か 決めようか好敵手
Let's decide who's strongest, rival!
速い者が勝つ 何言い訳はなしさ
The fast one wins, no excuses allowed.
よーいどーん！
Ready, set, go!
飛ばして飛ばして 涙さえ振り切って
Dash on, dash on, shaking off even tears,
前に足を出すんだ 悩む暇なんてない
put your foot forward, no time to hesitate.
答えを出すのは ゴールした後でも遅くない
Finding the answer isn't too late even after the goal.
抗えぬ本能
Unstoppable instinct,
譲れない頂上
the summit we cannot yield.
王者の雄叫びに 続け！
Continue the champion's roar!
Ready!! Steady!! Derby!!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
どんなことが起こったって レースが止まらないように
No matter what happens, so the race doesn't stop,
ずっと続いていく この友情
this friendship will go on forever.
憎まれ口を叩いたって
Even if we exchange snarky remarks,
みんな一列になれば
if we all line up together,
ah てっぺんめがけて 位置についてよーい！
ah, aiming for the top, on your mark, get set!
走って走って 憧れを追い越して
Run and run, overtaking our yearnings.
次は誰の番だ？
Whose turn is next?
さあ目指すはスーパースター
Now, aiming to be a superstar,
生きてく
Living...
意味なんて
What's the meaning of it...
ぶっちぎった後でついてくる
It follows right after breaking away,
勝ちたい！
I want to win!
そう、これは本能
Yes, this is instinct.
走りたい！
I want to run!
やまない衝動
An unceasing impulse.
勝利の雄叫びよ 轟け！
Roar, the shout of victory!
Ready!! Steady!! Derby!!
ひゃあぁぁ〜っ！！冷たーいっ！！
Whoa, so cold!! Freezing!!
バンドして汗かいちゃったからさ〜 リフレッシュ、リフレッシュ♪
We worked up a sweat rocking out, so... time to refresh!
ほら、大丸も早く進んで〜っ！！
Come on, Omaru, hurry up and move in!
あぁぁぁぁぁぁぁっ！！地獄シャワー、無理〜〜〜っ！！！
Aaaaaah!! This hell shower is impossible~~~!!!
シャワー浴びて、プールで泳いで遊んだら…きっといいアイディアも出てくるってば！
If we take a shower, swim, and play in the pool... I'm sure great ideas will come up!
…そう言って、毎回泳ぎ疲れて終わるんだけどね〜〜
...You always say that, and then we just get too tired from swimming and end it~
でもさ、夏といえばプールでしょ！ここで何かするのもアリじゃない？
But hey, summer means the pool! Wouldn't it be fun to do something here?
プールでできることといえば……撮影会！！
Speaking of what we can do in a pool... a photo shoot!!
ねねたちの水着姿で！
In our swimsuits!
お客さんを……悩殺♡
Knocking the fans... dead♡
ダメに決まってるだろ！！会長に怒られるよっ！！
That's obviously out of the question!! The principal will be furious!!
絶対盛り上がるのにな〜〜
But it would definitely get everyone hyped up~
……プールにラミちゃん沈めて、産地直送ラミ水……これは売れる！！
...Dunk Lamy in the pool, direct-from-the-source Lamy water... this will sell!!
そこっ！ラミから出汁とろうとするな！ラミ水は忘れろ！！
Hey! Don't try to extract dashi from Lamy! Forget Lamy water!
…じゃあ、ライブしとく？プールサイドで！
...Then how about a live performance? By the poolside!
まぁ…そうなるよね〜！でも夏、プール、歌…最高にマッチしてるっ！
Well... figures! But summer, pool, and songs... match each other perfectly!
いいねいいね！あの夏フェスの曲やろうよ〜！水鉄砲とか持って、みんなでびしょびしょになりながら！！
Sounds great! Let's play that summer fes song! With water guns, getting totally soaked together!!
え？でもあれってエモい感じの恋愛ソングじゃなかった……？
Eh? But wasn't that song an emotional romance song...?
それをわたしたちなりに歌い上げるってことよ！
That just means we sing it in our own style!
フェスにぴったりの選曲だからね！
It's the perfect song choice for a festival!
それじゃあ……終わらない夏にするぞーーっ！！！
Then let's make this... a never-ending summer!!!
おーーっ！！！
Yeah!!!
君と夏フェス
[Title: 君と夏フェス]
まだ照れ臭いあいつとフェスに
I made a promise to go to a festival with him, who's still shy,
行く約束をしたはいいけど
but if I get too carried away, I might scare him off.
あまりノってたら引かれそう
So I decided to enjoy it moderately.
控えめに楽しむって決めたんだ
But my favorite rock star—
でも私の大好きな
On the midsummer stage, wearing a suit,
ロックスター 真夏のステージで
I just can't hold it in anymore!
スーツを着たロックスター もう
My favorite rock star—
我慢できない!
I can't hold it in anymore!
止まらないのは私の汗
Is this sweat of mine won't stop,
それとも君への気持ち?
or is it my feelings for you?
滴り落ちてく恋心
Catching the love overflowing drop by drop,
こぼれないようにすくってね
my expectations for summer just won't stop.
止まらないのは夏への期待
This might be a summer I'll never forget.
忘れられない夏になるかも
Scorched by the midsummer sun,
夏の日差しで焼け焦げそう
everything turns into slow motion.
すべてがスローモーションになる
I don't care about anyone else's sweat,
他人の汗もどうでもよくて
and I don't even feel the scorching sun.
日差しの鬱陶しさも感じない
But my favorite rock star—
でも私の大好きなロックスター
At the end of the last song,
ラストの曲終わり ロックスター 帰ってく
the rock star heads back home.
ライブが終わって我に返って それから… それから…
The concert ends, and I return to my senses... and then...
ずいぶん前のほうに来ちゃってたみたい
It seems I've come quite a bit forward.
さっきまで二人がいた場所、もう違う景色
The scenery is completely different from where we were just a moment ago.
ああ、私やっちゃった 本気だったのに
Ah, I messed up, even though I was serious.
うつむく私の隣に君が
Hanging my head, you're right next to me.
私の目を見つめる君 時間が止まってるみたい
You gaze into my eyes, as if time has stopped.
少し笑って君は言う
With a slight smile, you say:
「新しい君が見れたから 今日は本当に来て良かった」
“I'm so glad I came today because I got to see a new side of you.”
照れ笑いの奥見えちゃそう で
Fearing you might see my embarrassed grin,
私は焦って目をそらした
I hurriedly looked away.
止まらないのは二人の恋だ
Our love won't stop.
今年の夏よ 終わらないでよ
Don't ever end, this summer of ours.
はぁ～～～～ 遊んだ遊んだ♪
Ah, we had so much fun!
もう、くったくた… で、結局なーんも決まってないっていう(笑)
Man, we're exhausted... See, in the end, nothing got decided (laughs).
制服、洗濯に出しちゃったし…… 今日のお衣装、いつもの着替えしかないよ～
My uniform is at the dry cleaners... Today's outfit is just our usual everyday wear~
もうこのままの格好でなんかやるしかないね～っ!
Well, we'll just have to do something in these outfits!~
でもさ、やっぱり私たちにできることって… 歌とダンス、かな～って思うんだよね～
But you know, I think what we do best is singing and dancing, right?
うん…変に着飾らずに、“いつものわたしたち”を見せるのが一番かも
Yeah... instead of dressing up weird, showing our "usual selves" might be best.
よっし!じゃあ歌う曲を決めようよ!! ねねは……エモい感じがいいな!いつもと違う感じの!
Alright! Let's decide on a song to sing!! Nene wants something emotional and different from usual!
ポルカは～～恋愛ソングやってみたいなっ♡
And Polka wants to try a love song!~
ラミィは元気いっぱい! 合いの手たっぷりなの盛り上がるやつ!!
Lamy wants something full of energy! With lots of call-and-response to hype everyone up!
歌詞がグッと心に来る系の曲もいいなあ～
Botan wants a song where the lyrics really tug at your heartstrings~
...
まぁ、みんな好みがバラバラだしね〜
Well, everyone's tastes are all over the place, huh?
でも全部は無理じゃない？
Don't you think doing all of them is a bit much?
いや、できる！！やってみなきゃ始まんないっ！
No, we can do it! If we don't try, nothing will start!
まさか…全部やる気？
No way... You're going to do all of them?
もちろん！どれか1つなんて勿体ないでしょっ！
Of course! Doing just one is such a waste, right?
全部やって、いいいがあるのか考えよう！
Let's do all of them and see which one is the best!
ちょっとは休憩入れさせてね…
I need to take a break first, though...
だったらさ、各自自分の部屋でやりたい曲やってこっ！
In that case, how about everyone does the song they want in their own room?
じゃあまずネネからねっ！
Then first up is Nene!
この曲は…ネネは違う服でやる！
This song... Nene is going to do it in a different outfit!
わかった。やろっか～
Got it. Shall we do it?
今度こそ…これで出汁物を決めるぞ～！
This time for sure... I'm going to nail this performance!
じゃあやりますか！ねね、着替え終わった？
Alright, shall we do it? Nene, are you done changing?
オッケー！それでは、いきま～す！！
Okey-dokey! Here we go!
もう忘れてしまったかな
Have I already forgotten it?
夏の木陰に座ったまま、
Sitting in the shade of summer,
アイスを口に放り込んで風を待っていた
popping ice pop into my mouth and waiting for the wind.
もう忘れてしまったかな 世の中の全部嘘だらけ
Have I forgotten it already? Everything in this world is just a lie.
本当の価値を二人で探しに行こうと笑ったこと
I laughed, saying we'd go find our true worth together.
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So I won't forget it, so it won't fade away...
形に残るものが全てじゃないように
So that everything isn't just what remains in physical form.
言葉をもっと教えて 夏が来るって教えて
Teach me more words, tell me summer is coming.
僕は描いてる 眼に映ったのは夏の亡霊だ
What I'm drawing and seeing in my eyes is a summer ghost.
風にスカートが揺れて 思い出なんて忘れて
The wind sways my skirt, making me forget any memories.
浅い呼吸をする、汗を拭って夏めく
Taking shallow breaths, wiping away sweat as summer passes.
もう忘れてしまったかな
Have I forgotten it already?
夏の木陰に座った頃
Around the time we sat in the shade of summer trees,
遠くの丘から顔出した雲があったじゃないか
wasn't there a cloud peeking out from the distant hill?
君はそれを掴もうとして、馬鹿みたいに空を切った手で
You tried to catch it, cutting through the empty air like a fool.
僕は紙に雲一つを描いて、笑って握って見せて
I drew a single cloud on paper, and showed you while smiling and gripping it.
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So I won't forget, so it won't fade away...
歴史に残るものが全てじゃないから
Because not everything is left behind in history.
今だけ顔も無くして 言葉も全部忘れて
Even losing my expression for now, forgetting all words...
君は笑ってる 夏を待っている僕ら亡霊だ
We are ghosts, smiling and waiting for the summer.
心をもっと教えて 夏の匂いを教えて
Teach me more of your heart, teach me the scent of summer,
浅い呼吸をする
taking shallow breaths.
忘れないように 色褪せないように
So I won't forget, so it won't fade away...
心に響くものが全てじゃないから
Because not everything is something that resonates in the heart.
言葉をもっと教えて さよならだって教えて
Teach me more words, tell me it's a goodbye.
今も見るんだよ 夏に咲いてる花に亡霊を
I still see it today, a ghost in the flowers blooming in summer.
言葉じゃなくて時間を 時間じゃなくて心を
Time instead of words, heart instead of time.
浅い呼吸をする、汗を拭って夏めく
Taking shallow breaths, wiping away sweat as summer passes.
夏の匂いがする
I can feel the scent of summer.
もう忘れてしまったかな 夏の木陰に座ったまま
Have I forgotten it already? Sitting in the shade of summer...
出会ってから付き合うまでのあの感じ
That feeling from when we met until we started dating
土曜日は 会えることが 当たり前になって
Saturdays became a given for us to meet,
不安からの あの気持ちが 消えてちょっと寂しいの
and that feeling of anxiety is gone, leaving me a little lonely.
一生分の キスの回数 すぐに超えちゃうよ
We'll instantly exceed a lifetime's worth of kisses.
まだ少し まだもっと
Still a little more, still a bit more,
特別でいたいの
I want to be special.
出会ってから付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's keep that feeling from when we met until we started dating.
わかってる ふりなんて 100年後もいらない
Pretending to understand—we won't need that even 100 years from now.
二人の合図が増えたって 大事なこと言おう
Even if our signals increase, let's say what's important.
夏の日の はじまりを 季節が 変わっても 覚えてて
Even if the seasons change, remember the start of that summer day.
月曜は 会えないなら 次の日はどうって？
If we can't meet on Monday, how about the next day?
繰り返しの 言葉だって それをもっと言ってよね
Even repetitive words, say those to me more.
一回だけの キスのために すぐに会いに来た
I came to see you right away for just that one kiss.
あのときの あの場所は 特別じゃないし
That place back then wasn't anything special, but...
ずっと 出会ってから 付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's always keep that feeling from when we met until we started dating.
素っ気ない ふりなんて かっこよくもないよ
Acting indifferent isn't cool at all.
間違いないこと増えたって 幸せちょっと違う
Even if certainties increase, happiness feels a bit different.
夏の日の はじまりが 正しい恋よ ほら 映してる
The start of that summer day reflects true love, look.
ずっと 出会ってから 付き合うまでの あの感じでいよう
Let's always keep that feeling from when we met until we started dating.
わかってる ふりなんて 100年後もいらない
Pretending to understand—we won't need that even 100 years from now.
二人の合図が増えたって 大事なこと言おう
Even if our signals increase, let's say what's important.
夏の日の はじまりを 季節が 変わっても 覚えてて
Even if the seasons change, remember the start of that summer day.
ドキッ！こういうのが恋なの？
Is this what love feels like?
ねえ 歌うわ
Hey, I'll sing.
そうよ あなたに
That's right, to you
甘えたいけれど 恥ずかしいかもね
I want to rely on you, but it might be embarrassing.
願い事の呪文 ほら ムニャムニャニャ〜
The spell of wishes, look, munyamunyanya~
ずっとこのまま 時が 止まらぬかもね
Time might just stop staying like this forever.
こういうのが恋なのの ドキドキドキー
This is what love is like, doki-doki-doki!
しかもね
What's more...
スキスキスキ
Suki, suki, suki!
昨日よりも…かもね
More than yesterday... maybe.
…かもね…かもね
...Maybe... maybe.
ねえ 歌って
Hey, sing along.
そうよ あなたも
That's right, you too.
乙女の気持ちが 伝わるといいな
I hope my maiden heart reaches you.
のどから出そうなくらい もう ラブラブラブ
Almost bursting out of my throat, ooh, love, love, love!
ずっとこのままあなた 素敵がいいな
I hope things stay this wonderful with you forever.
こういうのは初めて ドキドキドキー
This is my first time feeling like this, doki-doki-doki!
ああ いいな スキスキスキ
Ah, how nice, suki suki suki!
さっきよりも…いいな
Even better than before... how nice.
神様のヒマ潰し
[Song: God's Pastime]
いつだって新しいことに 君は心奪われるから
Because your heart is always captivated by something new,
クルクルと変わる お天気謎だらけ
Spinning and changing, full of mysterious weather.
いつだってTVをつけても 知りたいことは1つもないよ
Even if you turn on the TV anytime, there's not a single thing you want to know.
似たようなウワサ ばっかり謎がない
Just similar rumors everywhere, no mystery at all.
手に入れたいんだ 君の心の地図
I want to get my hands on the map of your heart.
Ah 探し出したい宝物のありか その心の奥を掴んで揺さぶるものは何? 考えてるだけで日が暮れる
Ah, the treasure I want to find. What is it that grips and shakes the depths of your heart? Just thinking about it makes the day end.
苦しくて切なくて楽しくて 日が暮れる
Painful, heartbreaking, yet fun, as the day fades away.
勘ぐってありえない想像 へこんだかと思えば笑ったり
Giving in to impossible suspicions, laughing right after feeling down,
あたしはあたしで 相当謎だらけ
I myself am full of quite enough mysteries.
ハマってしまったら 恋は迷路 Ah 角を曲がれば行き止まりばかり
Once you get hooked, love is a maze. Ah, turn a corner and it's always a dead end.
物語の鍵を握って 遊んでいるのは誰? ずいぶん悪趣味なヒマ潰し
Who is holding the key to the story and playing around? Such a rather bad-taste pastime.
骨を折って遊ぶ 神様のヒマ潰し
Breaking a sweat for amusement—God's pastime.
いつだって新しいことに
Whenever new things come along,
君は心奪われるから
you are captivated by them.
クルクルと変わるお天気 謎だらけ
The weather keeps changing, full of mysteries.
不安な夜は
When uneasy nights come...
チリリと鳴き通す
ring through the depths of my heart.
Ah 会えない理由はわかってるのに
Ah, I know why I can't meet you.
物語の鍵を握って遊んでいるのは誰?
Who is playing with the key to our story?
ずいぶん悪趣味な暇潰し
A rather malicious way to kill time.
その心の奥を掴んで揺さぶるものは何?
What is shaking the depths of my heart?
考えてるだけで日が暮れて
Just thinking about it makes the day end.
苦しくて切なくて楽しくて日が暮れて
Painful, poignant, joyful as the day fades.
この恋に明け暮れる
As this love dawns and fades away.
つっ……疲れた~~!!
Phew... I'm so tired~~!!
さすがに…金貝物連続は応えたね…
As expected... doing them all back-to-back really takes a toll...
でもでもっ! どの曲も最高だった~~♪
Even so!! Every song was just the best~~♪
うん…でも、"わたしたちらしさ"があるかって言われると…ちょっと悩むな~
Yeah... but being told we have "individuality" makes me wonder a bit~
(……)
まもなく、学寮祭が始まります。関係する生徒の皆さんは、速やかに準備をお願いします。
[Broadcast: The dormitory festival is about to begin. All students involved, please prepare promptly.]
やっ、やば~い!! もう始まっちゃうってば~っ!
Oh, no, no!! It's about to start, you guys!
え~~お腹すいた~ ちょっと購買行ってくるねっ!!
Man, I'm starving~. I'm gonna go hit the canteen!!
じゃ、私も行く~
Then I'm going too~.
ラミィも行く~!
Lamy is going too~!
えぇ~~!? ちょっと~~!?
Ehh~?! Wait a minute--?!
パン残ってるかな~ ……ん?あれって……なんだ??
Any bread left over~? ...Huh? What is that...?
こ、これは!
Th-This is...!
もしかして……!
Could it be...?!
もしれなくても!
Even if you say "couldn't be"!
間違いない!!!
No doubt about it!!!
NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade!
ねぽらぼ5周年グッズがこんなところにっ!
For NePoLaBo's 5th anniversary to be in a place like this!
きっと思いの配信終わりに出るやつだ!
I bet this is gonna drop right after today's stream!
気になる~~~~!
I'm so curious~~!
これは順番に見ていくしかないでしょ!
Well, obviously we've gotta check them out in order!
まずはプレミアムアクリル色紙!
First up is the Premium Acrylic Shikishi!
今回のグッズのテーマが花鳥風月!
The theme for this round's merch is Kachou Fuugetsu (Flowers, Birds, Wind, Moon).
七原しえさんが描いてくれました!ねねたちの和服姿、きれいでしょう?
Nanasora Shi-e-san drew this for us! Don't Nene's and the others' Japanese outfits look gorgeous?
アクリル色紙にはねねたちの複製サインとロゴが入ってます!アクリルの足も付いてるから、机に飾っておくこともできるよ!
The acrylic shikishi comes with Nene and the others' replicated signatures and logos, plus stand feet so you can display it on your desk!
めっちゃかわいいので、ぜひっ! 次!
It's super cute, so definitely check it out! Next!
続いてはオフィシャルホロカスリーブアニバーサリーパレードねぽらぼバージョン!もちろん、ホロカが入るスリーブです!1パック60枚入ってるから、これでねぽらぼデッキを作り上げてくだサイ!
Up next is the Official Holoca Sleeve - Anniversary Parade NePoLaBo Version! Naturally, it's sleeves made to fit Holoca cards, with 60 sleeves per pack so you can build your very own NePoLaBo deck!
いや、もう最近はねねぽらぼ全員で対戦したから、もうこれでお前のオリジナルのデッキ構築をして優勝していくんだ!
Lately, I've been jamming with all of NePoLaBo, so with these, you can build your very own original deck and go take the championship!
さあ、お前ならできる!やるしかない!見ているお前ら、ねぽらぼリスナー!お前ら頑張ってくれ~! 次!
Come on, if it's you guys, you can do it—you gotta do it! All you NePoLaBo listeners out there, give it your all! Next!
続いてはアクリルスタンド!
Next up is the Acrylic Stand!
「プレミアムアクリル色紙」とは別表情をしたラミィたちのアクリルスタンドです!
These are Lamy and the gang's acrylic stands featuring different expressions from the Premium Acrylic Shikishi.
花鳥風月で、花/春が桃鈴ねね、鳥/秋が獅白ぼたん、風/夏が尾丸ポルカ、月/冬が雪花ラミィとなっています!
For Kachou Fuugetsu, Flower/Spring is Momosuzu Nene, Bird/Autumn is Shishiro Botan, Wind/Summer is Omaru Polka, and Moon/Winter is Yukihana Lamy!
では次!
Now for the next one!
最後は記念メダル!専用のケースと巾着袋がついてくる記念メダルです!
Finally, the Commemorative Medal! A commemorative medal that comes with its own dedicated case and drawstring pouch.
それぞれタレントカラーと名前が入っていて、期生ごとにデザインが違うので、コレクションアイテムとしてぜひ揃えてみてください!
Each features their talent color and name, with unique designs for each generation member, so be sure to collect them all as a collection item!
以上、ねぽらぼアニバーサリーパレードのグッズでした!
And that's all for the NePoLaBo Anniversary Parade merch!
それでは──これより、学寮祭を開始いたします
"Well then—we will now begin the dormitory festival."
ご来場の皆様、どうぞ最後までお楽しみください
"To all visitors, please enjoy it until the very end."
やばい！学寮祭始まってるって！
"Oh no! The dormitory festival is starting!"
ねねたちも行かなきゃ！
"We have to go too!"
結局、何も買えなかったんだけど！
"After all, we couldn't buy anything!"
しゃーなし。戻って学寮祭の話をしますか...
"Oh well. Shall we go back and talk about the dormitory festival..."
で、えーっと、これは、何をしているの？？
"So, um, what are we doing here??"
ねねたちには、歌とダンスしかないっ！！ならばギリギリまで、全力で練習するしかないっしょーー！！
"Nene and the others only have singing and dancing!! In that case, we have no choice but to practice with all our might until the very end!!"
でも、もうお客さん入ってるけどね(笑)
"But the audience is already in, though (lol)."
あぁぁっ、もうやるしかないっ！！
"Aahh, we have no choice but to do it now!!"
でもさ、肝心の「何やるか」決めてないのでは？
"But wait, haven't you decided on the most important part—what we're actually going to do?"
(……)
"(......)"
……でもさ、お客さんたちが観たいのって、やっぱり「わたしたちらしさ」だよね。
"......But you know, what the audience wants to see is definitely 'our true selves'."
それなら……オリ曲じゃない？
"In that case... isn't it our original song?"
じゃあ、全部やろう！！
"Then let's do all of them!!"
また～～～！？！？
"Again~~!?!?"
1つだけじゃダメダメっ！衣装もぜーんぶ着替えて、たくさん歌おうよ！
"Just one is no good, no good! Let's change all our outfits and sing lots of songs!"
メドレーってこと！？いいじゃんそれ！！
"A medley!? That sounds great!!"
おぉ～、いいかも！
"Ohh, sounds good!"
で、順番はどうするの？？
"So, what about the order??"
そんなん、パッションでどうにかなるなるっ！！
"That kind of thing will somehow work out with passion!!"
こりゃ大変なことになりそうですね…
"This is going to be a disaster..."
うーん……
"Hmm......"
ししろん？どうしたの？？
"Shishiron? What's wrong??"
いや、何か忘れている気がするんだけど…思い出せない…
"Well, I feel like I'm forgetting something... I can't remember..."
大丈夫大丈夫っ！これを歌えば学寮祭は、ねねたちのものっ！！
"It's okay, it's okay! If we sing this, the dormitory festival is Nene and the gang's!!"
よっしゃいくぞーー！！
"All right, let's go!!"
“わたしたちらしさ”見せるよ！
"We'll show 'our true selves'!"
うんっ。とりあえず、やるだけやろう！せーのっ！
"Yeah. For now, let's just do what we can! Ready, set!"
ねぽらぼメドレー！！
"Nepolabo Medley!!"
手を上げて
"Raise your hands,"
clap your hands 海の向こうまで
"clap your hands, across the sea,"
clap your hands 届きますように
"clap your hands, may it reach you."
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
"Clap your hands, clap your hands."
光射す 僕たちの未来
"Shining light, our future."
始めようか さあDiving
"Shall we begin? Now, diving,"
待ってても意味ないTiming
"timing where waiting means nothing,"
あの魚みたいにSwimming Swimming
"swimming, swimming like that fish,"
でもたまに止まってThinking Thinking
"but occasionally stopping to think, think."
変えてみせるChange
"Change that shows a transformation,"
踏み出すのさStepping
"stepping as we take a step forward,"
掴んでみせるよ キラキラMy Dream
"I'll show you I can grasp it, my sparkling dream."
叶う日までStory繋ぐから
"Connecting the story until the day it comes true,"
だって君にずっと見ていてほしいから
"because I want you to keep watching forever."
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
"Raise your hands, clap your hands, across the sea,"
clap your hands 届きますように
"clap your hands, may it reach you."
手を叩こう 手を叩こう 手を叩こう
"Clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands."
ほら一緒に Everybody
"Hey, everyone, together,"
clap your hands 空の向こうまで
"clap your hands, beyond the sky,"
clap your hands 響きますように
"clap your hands, may it resound."
手を叩こう 手を叩こう 手を叩こう
"Clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands."
光射す 僕たちの未来
"Shining light, our future."
Hyper Jumpin' Now
子どもくらいはしゃぐほうがお得でしょ
"it's more profitable to act as playful as a child."
低気圧から這い上がっていくテンション
"Tension climbing up from low atmospheric pressure."
このままスピード加速して
"Accelerating speed just like this,"
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
"I wonder what awaits us at our destination."
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
"Give our unstoppable feelings a running start,"
次元を超えて行こう
"let's go beyond dimensions."
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
"Now, Hyper Jumpin', let's jump around,"
ハイになって灰になるまでダンシング Shake it up
"dancing until we go high and turn to ash, shake it up."
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
"Hyper Jumpin' beyond the sky,"
もっともっと近づきたいの
"I want to get closer, more and more."
Woh...
ドキドキしたい キミキミキミ愛
"Wanna feel my heart pounding, you, you, you love."
Woh...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
"I want to fly higher and higher."
Disは No No
"Dis is no no,"
好きなら More More More
"if you like it, more, more, more."
邪魔するノイズは打ち消せ Bang Bang Bang
"Bash away the disturbing noise, bang, bang, bang."
遊みたいだけ アンチは無視して
"Just want to play, ignore the antis,"
笑い飛ばして 蹴飛ばせ Kick it!
"laugh it off, kick 'em away, kick it!"
so let's go!
どこまでも 踏み出そう
Let's step out everywhere,
銀河のまんなか 笑い合って
laughing together in the galaxy,
Wonderful Tour!
一歩目が既に異空間
The first step is already another dimension,
キラリ 渦に巻き込まれた？
Did you get caught in a sparkling vortex?
違うよ 出会いたくて
No, we wanted to meet you,
ホラ みんなここにいる
Look, everyone is here.
夢のようで…
It's like a dream...
だけどね
But,
ファンタジーじゃない予感
This feeling isn't just fantasy,
流星群
A meteor shower—
負けないよう
So we won't lose,
光放って！
Release the light!
どんな憧れも飛び越えて
Jumping over any longing,
銀河のまんなか行進しよう
Let's march through the middle of the galaxy.
キラめきのシンフォニーさ
It's a symphony of sparkle,
足跡だって星になる
Even our footprints become stars.
1, 2, 3… Yeah！
1, 2, 3... Yeah!
奇跡散りばめ
Scattering miracles,
1, 2, 3… Yeah！
1, 2, 3... Yeah!
何万光年を
Through tens of thousands of light-years,
1, 2, 3… Yeah！
1, 2, 3... Yeah!
旅してゆく季節が今
The season of our journey now
始まったんだよきっと！
Has surely begun!
Wonderful Tour！
Wonderful Tour!
キミに届け 星のメロディー
Reaching you, the melody of the stars,
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Stuffing our feelings tight inside,
キミと奏でる このハーモニー
Playing this harmony with you,
これからも ずっと続いてく
It will continue on forever.
ねぇねぇ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey hey, come closer to me!
回り始めた世界で踊らない？終わらない
Won't you dance in the world that began to spin? It never ends.
わくわく 魔法かけたら
When excitement casts its magic,
ドキドキはSyncしてほらParty Time 止まらない
Heartbeats sync up, look, Party Time won't stop.
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
Putting in our wish,
Twinkle Twinkle 夜空で歌いましょう
Twinkle Twinkle, let's sing in the night sky.
君に響け 星のメロディー
Resound to you, the melody of the stars,
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a brand new constellation,
君と繋がっているこの宇宙(そら)に
In this universe connected with you,
宝石を 散りばめよう
Let's scatter jewels all around.
Twinkle 4 You
君に響け 星のメロディー
Resound to you, the melody of the stars,
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a brand new constellation,
君と繋がっているこの宇宙(そら)に
In this universe connected with you,
宝石を 散りばめよう
Let's scatter jewels all around.
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reaching you, the melody of the stars,
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Stuffing our feelings tight inside,
キミと奏でる このハーモニー
Playing this harmony with you,
これからも ずっと続いてく
It will continue on forever.
La La La La...
やっぱねぽらぼだな～！！
As expected, it's NePoLaBo!
これで学寮祭は――大成功～！！
With this, the school dormitory festival is a huge success!
う～ん……
Hmm...
えっ、ししろん？どうしたの？
Eh, Shishiron? What's wrong?
いやさー、確かに良かったんだけど……なんかこう……何かを忘れてる気がするんだよね。
Well, I mean, it was definitely great, but... somehow it feels like... we're forgetting something.
なに言ってんの！？いやこのメドレーで完璧だってば！
What are you talking about?! This medley was totally perfection!
そうだよ～！これでみんないっしょになってハッピー！！
That's right! That way, we all became one and we're happy!
来てくれた人たちも、きっとラミィたちの声を聞いて、喜んでくれたよ！
The people who came definitely heard our voices and rejoiced!
ひとつ……声……あっ！
One... voice... Ah!
私たち、新曲作ってたじゃん！！
We made a new song together!!
あっ……
Ah...
わすれてたぁーー！！！
We forgot--!!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのにっ！！
And Nene and everyone practiced so much for it!!
ねねたち、あんなに練習したのにっ!!
We practiced so much for this!!
作ったのはいいけど……「出すタイミングどうしよう」って言ってたら、
I mean, we made it... but while we were saying "When should we release it?",
完全に忘れてた……
we completely forgot...
出すタイミング絶対にここだったな〜
The timing to release it was definitely right here~
もうステージ真っ暗だしい〜〜っ！
The stage is completely pitch black now~~!
お客さん……まだいてくれてる、かな……
I wonder... if the audience is still here...
大丈夫！今なら、まだ……ギリギリ間に合うっ!!
It's fine! If we do it now, we can... just barely make it in time!!
ねぇ！えっと、そこの君!! まだ……見てくれてるよね？
Hey! Um, you right there!! You're still... watching, right?
ねねたちの新しい曲——聞いてくれる？
Will you listen to... our new song?
うんうん……きっと、聞いてくれるって信じてる！
Yeah, yeah... I'm sure you'll listen, I believe in you!
最後まで一緒に盛り上がっていこうね！
Let's get hyped together until the very end!
それでは——改めて……んっ……聞いてください——ねポラボの新曲です！
And now—once more... *clears throat*... please listen—it's Nepolabo's new song!
この先、みんなとなら、どこまでもいけると願って——歌います
Hoping that with everyone, we can go anywhere—we sing this.
5周年——その先の未来もずっと一緒に見守り……歩んでください
5th anniversary—please keep watching over and walking with us into the future beyond...
1人じゃたどり着けない場所へ……みんなで——
To a place we couldn't reach alone... together with everyone—
ひとつになる声
voices becoming one.
暗闇の中で 見つけた声
In the darkness, the voice I found
そのしるべを 辿りながら
following that guiding sign,
僕らは 走るよ
we are running on.
ひとりぼっちだった日 先見えなかった日
The days I was all alone, the days I couldn't see ahead,
だけど君と出会えて そっと扉を開けた
but when I met you, I softly opened the door.
手のひらの中に また1を足して 何度も奇跡を叶えよう
Adding one more to the palm of my hand, let's make miracles come true time and again.
澄み渡る空の彼方 太陽と踊る
Beyond the clear sky, dancing with the sun,
羽になる 情熱が突き動かす
becoming wings, passion drives us forward.
僕らの明日を 照らして
Illuminating our tomorrow,
同じ夢を駆ける 僕らは強く心を結んで
Running toward the same dream, we bind our hearts strongly together,
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから これからまた続いてく道
because we can go anywhere to the ends of the earth, along the path continuing from here.
1人じゃたどり着けない だから この背中預けるよ
A place we couldn't reach alone—that's why I entrust you with my back.
信じている 君の手を
Believing in your hand,
僕らの未来を みんなの声を
our future, everyone's voice.
君らしって思う その積み重ねが なぜか嬉しくなるの
Thinking "that's so like you," for some reason all those accumulated moments make me happy.
きっと これからもそう 手のひらのなかの 大切な日々が
Surely, it will be the same from now on, precious days in the palm of our hand
たくさんの光を奏でて 君と笑った
playing countless lights, as I smiled with you.
始まりの時の願い 今もほら 輝いている
The wish from the beginning is still shining, look.
未来まで連れてゆこう
Let's carry it all the way to the future.
暗闇を抜けた先に みんなの笑顔 見つけた
Beyond the darkness, we found everyone's smiles.
同じ夢を駆ける 僕らは強く心を結んで
Running toward the same dream, we bind our hearts strongly together,
世界の果て どこにでも行けるから これからまた続いてく道
because we can go anywhere to the ends of the earth, along the path continuing from here.
1人じゃたどり着けない だから この背中預けるよ
A place we couldn't reach alone—that's why I entrust you with my back.
信じている 君の手を 僕らの未来を みんなの声を ひとつに
Believing in your hand, our future, everyone's voice, becoming one.
みんなの声をと
Gathering everyone's voices...
重ねて
Layering them together,
みんなの声をと
Gathering everyone's voices...
ひとつに
into one.
みんなの声をと
Gathering everyone's voices...
重ねて
Layering them together,
みんなの声をと
Gathering everyone's voices...
ひとつに
into one.
心合わせて
Matching our hearts,
重ねて
layering them together,
僕らは願う
we make a wish.
ひとつに
As one,
光の中で
in the midst of the light,
重ねて
layering them together,
ひとつになる声
a voice that becomes one.